wiliam.com.au 2019-03-11

# Legal | Wiliam Digital Agency

Wiliam is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We have structured our website so that, in general, you can visit Wiliam on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your contact/client relationship with Wiliam.

This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers the five foundation principles of fair information:   
• Awareness   
• Choice   
• Accuracy & Access   
• Security   
• Oversight 

**Awareness**

Wiliam provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every wiliam.com.au page, including pages found within our client system and subdomains. 

**What we collect**

On some Wiliam websites, you can subscribe to different events and seminars, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and some preference information. 

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your professional interests, demographics and more detailed contact preferences. 

Our electronic newsletters record anonymous data about articles you have expressed interest in. Some wiliam.com.au web pages use cookies, a data analysis technique.

**How the information is Used**

Wiliam uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service, whether as a visitor of the firm, contact or client. 

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. We will also follow local requirements, such as allowing you to opt in before receiving unsolicited contact, where applicable.

**Who it is shared with**

Wiliam will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other Wiliam entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described in "how we use it". Such Wiliam entities and/or business partners are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.

**Choice**

Wiliam will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honour such requests. 

Your permission is always secured first, should we ever share your information with third parties that are not acting on our behalf and governed by our privacy policy.

**Accuracy and Access**

Wiliam strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. 

We will provide you with access to your information, including making every effort to provide you with online access to your registration data so that you may view, update or correct your information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or enabling you to make corrections. To access your personally identifiable information, return to the web page where you originally entered it and follow the instructions on that web page. To opt-out of Wiliam contact, provide your name, email and/or address and relevant information about subscriptions or registrations you may have with Wiliam. 

This opt-out will cancel all marketing and support communication and newsletters, including offline subscriptions. Certain areas of Wiliam's Websites may limit access to specific individuals through the use of passwords and through providing personally data. 

Links to third party websites on the site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Wiliam site. Wiliam has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. 

Thus, Wiliam does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so at your own risk.

**Security**

Wiliam is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data.

**The use of Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of text asking permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. If you agree, then your browser adds the text in a small file. The purpose of a cookie is to help us analyse Web traffic or let us know when you visit a particular site. 

Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes. For example, when you visit an electronic store, a cookie makes it easy to shop by allowing you to drop things into a shopping cart; the cart itself is not the cookie, the cookie is placed on your hard drive and keeps track of your cart versus others' in use at the same time. 

Wiliam uses traffic log cookies to identify what pages are being used and which ones aren't. This helps us aggregate and analyse data about Web page traffic and make improvements to wiliam.com.au web to better meet our visitor, contact and client needs. In this case, Wiliam uses this information only for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. That is the case of many of our support and information-sharing pages and forums. Denial of a traffic log cookie should not prevent you from using one of these sites. 

A few wiliam.com.au Websites use temporary cookies as part of the customer web navigation experience, tracking unique IDs for that particular Website session only. 

Examples are newlsetter registration sites. This cookie, by itself, only tells us that a previous wiliam.com.au visitor, contact or client has returned. If you deny the cookie, you can still use the site anonymously. At client.wiliam.com.au, you will receive a persistent cookie. Clients (and users of Wiliam's online client system) can browse some areas of client.wiliam.com.au with cookies turned off, but you can only browse the secure area of the site if you accept the cookie. 

Overall, cookies help us give you a better website to use, by letting us monitor what's working and what isn't through site traffic analysis. Wiliam wants to be sure you understand that accepting a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you chose to share with us. This practice is strictly enforced. We know that a lot of people have concerns about cookies, but in talking with many of our visitors, contacts and clients, we believe that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. We value the relationships we have with our visitors, users and clients, so we respect these concerns. Wiliam works to continuously improve the wiliam.com.au Web experience and personal data privacy policy and practices. 

You may set your Web browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests or decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contains cookies; those files are stored as part of your Internet browser.
